It's Big Adventure! It's Big Laughs! It's Big Bird on the Big Screen!
Follow That Bird is a family, comedy, adventure film directed by Ken Kwapis.
Big Bird is sent to live far from Sesame Street by a pesky social worker, who
thinks it would be better for him to live with other birds.
Unhappy, Big Bird runs away from his foster home, prompting the rest of the
Sesame Street gang to go on a cross-country journey to find him.
Big Bird / Oscar the Grouch / Bruno the Trashman
(voice), played by Caroll Spinney.
Kermit the Frog / Ernie (voice), played by Jim Henson.
Cookie Monster / Bert / Grover / Additional Muppets (voice), played by Frank Oz.
Gladys the Cow / Feathered Friends Owl / Additional Muppets
/ Grouches (voice), played by Richard Hunt.
Feathered Friends Magistrate / Grouch Diner Patron / Little Girl /
Additional Muppets (voice), played by Kathryn Mullen.
Count von Count / Herry Monster / Additional
Muppets (voice), played by Jerry Nelson.
Sesame Street Presents: Follow That Bird (or simply Follow That Bird) is a 1985 American family
musical comedy film directed by Ken Kwapis, and written by Tony Geiss and Judy Freudberg.
Based on the children's television series Sesame Street, it
was the series' first theatrical feature film.
It stars Muppet performers Caroll Spinney, Jim Henson and Frank Oz alongside Sandra
Bernhard, John Candy, Chevy Chase, Joe Flaherty, Waylon Jennings, and Dave Thomas.
It was filmed at the Cinespace Film Studios and on
location in the Greater Toronto Area.
Follow That Bird was theatrically released in the United States on
August 2, 1985, by Warner Bros., and grossed $14 million.
It received mostly positive reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of farm, friendship, airplane, airport, waitress.
The tone is lighthearted.